IHON VERA



WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Software Developer (ADSI - SENA) and in academic training as a Systems Engineer at the University of Ibagué (5th semester), with more than 3 years of work experience focused on Front-End development for various companies.

Solid knowledge in HTML, CSS, Boostrap, JavaScript, TypeScript, React among others. In addition, a good command of Wordpress, Woocommerce and Shopify.

CONTACT



Phone Number +57 311 8961906



Email Jhonvera.dev@gmail.com



Website www.Addevsoft.com



Git Hub www.github.com/JhonveraDev



Location Ibagué, Colombia.

EDUCATION

Year: 2020 - Present **Engineering of** Systems.

University of Ibague.

Year: 2015 - 2017 Software Technologist. SENA - A.D.S.I.



WORK EXPERIENCE

March 2022 - Present.

Course Developer | TMX

SweetRush Inc, United States.

- Creation and development of web courses.
- Resolve JIRA tickets on course design and/or logic.
- Content and design management in Figma.
- Communication with clients to finalize designs.
- Technologies used: HTML, SCSS, JavaScript, React, Adapt, Figma, GitLab, GitKraken, SVN and Jira.

December 2021 - March 2022

Front-End Developer

3Generaciones, Bogotá Colombia.

- Development of websites in WordPress and HTML templates.
- Creation of graphic pieces for web content.
- Creation and administration of advertising guidelines.
- Consulting clients to define designs.
- Website optimization.
- Technologies used: Wordpress [Elementor], Woocommerce, Shopify, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Adobe Illustrator.

JHON VERA

COMPETENCES

- Analysis and decision.
- Collaborative mindset.
- Attention to performance.
- Passion to learn.
- Adaptability and flexibility.
- Teamwork.
- Patience and persistence.
- Good communication.

REFERENCES

- David Vargas Software Engineer Contact: [+57] 321 4594369
- Duván Hernández Software Engineer Contact: [+57] 319 5769790
- Fernando Vera Software Engineer Contact: [+57] 314 3727739
- Julián GálvezDiseñador GráficoContact: [+57] 315 6158725

INTERESTS





WORK EXPERIENCE

March 2021 - August 2021

Front-End Developer Baha Agency, Australia.

- baria Agericy, Australia.
- Creation of graphic pieces for web content.

Development of custom websites.

- Maintenance and optimization in Wordpress.
- Technologies used: Wordpress [DIVI WPB],
 Woocommerce, Shopify, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ionic and Adobe Illustrator.

December 2018 - February 2020

Front-End Developer

Movidagráfica, Bogotá Colombia.

- Development of websites in Wordpress and templates.
- Creation of graphic pieces for web content.
- Maintenance and optimization in Woocommerce and Shopify.
- Technologies used: Wordpress [Elementor],
 Woocommerce, Shopify, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and
 Adobe Illustrator.

October 2017 - December 2018

Front-End Developer

Criminalistics Academy - Ibagué Colombia.

- Creation of administrative system for case studies.
- Establish a registration system for new students.
- Design graphic pieces for web content and social networks.
- Technologies used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL, PHP and Adobe Illustrator.



PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

SKILLS

HTML - SAS	WORDPRESS
JAVASCRIPT - TYPESCRIPT	SHOPIFY
SQL SERVER	FIGMA
REACT JS	ILLUSTRATOR